http://softwarefordentists.com/index.php/privacy-policy.html

DMC Dental
Log inContactPress
HomeDental softwareDental software for the front officeDental softwarePatient schedulingDocument managementPatient statementsFree DAISY dental software overview DVDClinical charting softwareCharting softwarePeriodontal chartingFree DAISY dental software overview DVDPatient education softwareDental mobile app - DAISY MobileDigital X-ray softwareComputer hardwareHardware and installation packagesComputers, keyboards and monitorsSignature pads and scannersData backup and protectionDigital radiographyDigital radiography advantagesWhy DMC? Five things you need to knowPain-free digital X-ray system upgradesTop dental X-ray systems3D Cone BeamVatech PaX-i3D cone beamVatech PaX-i 3D Green CT2D Digital Pan-CephVatech PaX-i for orthodonticsVatech PaX-i digital panoramic X-ray2D Digital X-RayEVA digital sensorsXDR digital sensorsVatech EzSensorClio X-ray sensorVatech PaX-i digital panoramic X-rayIntraoral CamerasClaris intra-oral cameraIRIS intra-oral cameraX-ray imaging softwareEz3D imaging softwareProducts & servicesDownload brochureGo paperlessElectronic prescribingInsurance payment postingElectronic claims attachmentsDocument managementSignature pads and scannersAutomate business processesData backup and protectionPatient communicationPatient statementsClaims processingPatient recall cardsHR ServicesOverviewCo-employmentOur AdvantageContact UsIncrease appointmentsAutomated appointment reminderDental practice marketingPatient recall cardsGet paid fasterInsurance payment postingNEA FastAttachInsurance claims submissionReal time eligibilityProcess electronic paymentsCybersecurity for dentistsProtect your practicePrevent embezzlementFree dental fraud ebookTraining & supportDAISY knowledge baseDAISY user log inRecall card selectionDAISY user trainingBusiness MattersAbout DMCDMC customer testimonialsContact DMCDental blogUpcoming eventsDigital radiography eventsDental software eventsCalendar
Developed in conjunction with Ext-Joom.com
Skip to content
You are here:
Privacy policy
Privacy policy and terms of use
Print
Email
Information you provide: We collect information affirmatively provided by you, such as survey information and/or site registrations.
Website usage information: We use your IP address to help diagnose problems and to administer our Web site. We do not link your IP address to any personally identifiable information. We use tracking information to determine which areas our site users visit based on traffic to those areas. Dentists Management Corporation (DMC) does not track what individual users read, but rather how often each page is visited. This helps us improve site usability and content for our users.
Dentists Management Corporation does not otherwise retain information about consumers who browse our Web page. Our Web server does not automatically recognize information regarding the domain or e-mail address used to access the Web page.
Collection and Use of Information: The information we collect is used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site and used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes. In addition, if you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not want to receive such communications from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an e-mail at the address set forth below or calling us at the telephone number provided.
From time to time, we may use customer information for new purposes not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.
Maintaining the privacy of your information is of paramount importance to us as it helps foster confidence, goodwill and stronger relationships with you, our customers. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please feel free contact dmcinfo@dmcdental.com.
Correction of Information: Upon request, we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information.
Sharing of Information: Dentists Management Corporation shares information obtained from consumers in only the following situations:
You have consented to the proposed use or disclosure;
With an affiliate, subsidiary or agent of Dentists Management Corporation and only for purposes specified in our privacy policy, as may be modified from time to time; or
Such information is required or permitted to be disclosed by law.
Cookies: Many Web pages use cookies to collect information about an individual’s activities on a particular Web site. However, Dentists Management Corporation does not set any cookies. The information we obtain from you is limited to that information you voluntarily disclose.
Security Practices: Dentists Management Corporation seeks to protect online information in accordance with applicable laws and industry practices. We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information within our control; however, we cannot guarantee the confidentiality or security of electronic transmissions because they may be sent via unsecured computers or links, and such information may be intercepted by unauthorized parties during the transmission process.
We will promptly notify you if we learn of any interception or misuse of your information.
Contact Information:
The contact information for Dentists Management Corporation is as follows:
601 SW Second Avenue Portland, Oregon 97204-3154 (503) 765-3471
Dentists Management Corporation can also be reached via e-mail at dmcinfo@dmcdental.com.
Terms of use
By using this website, you agree to abide by these terms and conditions.
Copyright: Copyright © 1996-2005 Health Services Group, Inc. All Rights Reserved. All items on this site web, including, but not limited to, the design, content, files and graphics, remain the property of Dentists Management Corporation, Health Services Group, Inc. and its suppliers. A single copy of these items may be downloaded and/or reprinted by you solely for your personal and non-commercial use. Any downloaded or reprinted materials may not be altered in any way and must contain the following copyright notice. "Copyright © 1996-2003 Health Services Group, Inc. All Rights Reserved." and any other copyright or other proprietary rights notices that were contained in the downloaded material. Any other use of the material, in whole or in part, for any other reason is expressly prohibited unless prior written consent is obtained from Dentists Management Corporation.
Trademarks: "DAISY" "Dentists Management Corporation" "DMC" and the names of all DAISY products and services referenced in the DAISY site are either trademarks or registered trademarks of Dentists Management Corporation or Health Services Group, Inc. Other product and company names referenced in the DAISY site may be the trademarks of their respective owners.
Disclaimers: All information contained within our site is provided on an "as is" and "as available" basis, without warranties of any kind, express or implied. DAISY hereby disclaims all warranties and conditions with regard to any information contained in this site, including any implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. DAISY assumes no liability of any kind for the information and data contained in this site, for your use of the site, the information or data contained herein, or for your inability to access this site.
Links to Third Party Sites: Certain links on this site will let you leave the DAISY site. The linked sites are not under the control of DAISY and DAISY is not responsible for the contents of any linked site. These links are provided for your convenience and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by DAISY of any such linked site.
Future Changes: We may find the need to update or change our terms and conditions statement in the future. We reserve the right to make such changes and will post a new terms and conditions statement should that situation occur.
DAISY DVD overview
Contact DMC
10505 SE 17th Ave.
Milwaukie, OR 97222
800-368-6401
Email DMC
Log inContactPressSitemapPrivacy policy
Copyright © 2011 Health Services Group, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
feedback
